Darko Djokic

Senior 3D Website & WebGL & Unity Game developer

+18125817202

Belgrade, Serbia

S live:.cid.3414237e4a0428af

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/darko-djokic-22b615301/

Profile

Experienced Game Developer | Graphics Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the Game Development industry and field of 2D/3D Rendering. Skilled in Unity3D, WebGL, Casual Games, Gameplay Programming, Multiplayer, PC, Console, Web, and Mobile Games. I have worked on world-class projects in India as well as in Malaysia, China, Singapore, Thailand, Indonesia on-site. And freelance for worldwide clients.

GAME ENGINES

- Unity3D, Unreal Engine, GameMaker WEB GAME ENGINES
- HTML5 Canvas, WebGL, ThreeJS, BabylonJS, PlayCanvas, Construct3, PixiJS, ImpactJS, Phaser.IO

GAME DESIGNS

- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Flash, 3D Max, Maya, Spine, ZBrush

WebGL Developer

Inmagine Innovation Sdn. Bhd

BACKEND

- SmartFox Server, Photon Server, UNet, Player.IO, Node.JS, WebSockets, Socket.IO, MySQL, PHP, AWS

PLATFORMS

- PC, Mac, Consoles, iOS, Android, Windows UWP, Windows Phone, WebGL, Google Cardboard, Steam, Daydream, Facebook Gameroom.

Professional Experience

2018/05 - 2019/04

2021/12 - 2023/12	Senior Software Engineer Team Lead Excellarate Creating and Implementing stunning WebGL Graphics Visualization for one of the world's largest providers of products and services to the energy industry.
2020/07 - 2021/06	Senior WebGL Developer Verdiseno, Inc This role involves implementing new capabilities to the front end of a WebGL-based graphical design tool and increasing test coverage using Three.js, React.js, Mobx, and Storybook. Lyra Solar and Solar Design Tool.
2020/01 - 2021/01	Unity Game Developer Terahard Ltd Worked on a world class upcoming fighter game in Unity3D using DOTS and ECS Jobs system. https://store.steampowered.com/app/417130/Era/
2019/07 - 2019/12	Graphics Engineer Homevista Decor and Furnishings Pvt. Ltd Worked on a 3D virtual interior design platform for the browser using WebGL and ThreeJS. http://spacecraft.homelane.com

Worked on world class image editing WebGL Projects and

WebGL Games http://www.pixlr.com/x/ | http://www.pixlr.com/e/

2017/03 - 2018/07

Frontend Developer

Beats by Dre

Contributed to fully rebuild the front-end with React and Redux.

Fashioned CSS to exactingly style to match received artwork and keep interactive and responsive style.

Replied with near immediate updates to requested changes from the Dr. Dre project manager.

-HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React, Redux

• • • • •

2014/07 - 2017/04

Game Developer

Logic Simplified

Game Development in Unity3D ,ImpactJS, JavaScript-WebGL, Node.JS, Socket.IO for Multiple Mobile and Desktop Devices. The job responsibility in this company includes development of 2D and 3D games in Unity3D-C# after the assets are provided by the design team. I have also developed games for web browsers here using Three.JS, ImpactJS and Phaser libraries.

Skills

Programming

Languages/Frameworks

Python, C#, Go, Ruby, C/C++, JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, Ruby, React, Next.js, Vue, Angular, Express, Django, Flask, FastAPI, Three.js, WebGL, Web3, HTML 5, Html, CSS.

Cloud Computing

AWS, GCP, Axure, Sagemaker

AI Techniques

Natural Language Processing, Machine Learning, Computer Vision, Data Science, Deep Learning, Image Processing, LLMs, Langchain, Pinecone, ChatGPT, OpenAI, Chatbot, TTS, STT

.

Education

2014/09 - 2018/04

Master's degree

ITS – Visoka škola strukovnih studija za informacione tehnologije Information Technology